2016 and here's some of the news beyond
the headlines Peruvian authorities are
investigating allegations that the
country's army is trafficking weapons 53
grenades were found inside a home in a
suburb of the capital last week police
say they've insulted gangs who use them
to threaten and extort civilians a bomb
technician died earlier this month after
a grenade he was trying to defuse
exploded outside of school North Korea
but its main nuclear complex stock
online on Tuesday the atomic reactor the
young beyond nuclear site was updated
and restarted
officials say they're working to improve
the quality and quantity of their
nuclear weapons plant was shut down in
2007 under an agreement with five
countries including the United States
and China in exchange for improved
relations and economic aid president has
deflected blame for Europe's growing
migrant crisis in an interview on
russian television was shot in acid said
foreign support for extremists in Syria
has caused an accident that a political
solution is possible only after the
fighting ends more than three million
people have fled Syria since the
conflict began in 2011 hundreds of
thousands are seeking asylum in western
europe a female boxer in england is
encouraging other muslim women to take
up sports by designing an athletic a job
many veiled Muslim girls are reluctant
to exercise in front of men because
they're not supposed to show their hair
the hijab we definitely empower them and
make them feel they can take part in
sport and be taken seriously
rather than walking to a gym at not
having the right head gear or not hijab
born in England Muslim girls have the
lowest board participation rate among
Buddhists Sikhs and Hindus
check on YouTube channel for more
original reporting and documentaries
from around the world have been Armenian
to russia has been adamant about not
allow mother of the mind I would not be